/*BEGIN_OF_INSERTION_SORT*/
    插入排序（Insertion Sort），有一个已经有序的数据序列，要求在这个已经排好的数据序列中插入一个数，但要求插入后此数据序列仍然有序，这个时候就要用到一种新的排序方法——插入排序法,插入排序的基本操作就是将一个数据插入到已经排好序的有序数据中，从而得到一个新的、个数加一的有序数据，算法适用于少量数据的排序，时间复杂度为O(n^2)。是稳定的排序方法。插入算法把要排序的数组分成两部分：第一部分包含了这个数组的所有元素，但将最后一个元素除外（让数组多一个空间才有插入的位置），而第二部分就只包含这一个元素（即待插入元素）。在第一部分排序完成后，再将这个最后元素插入到已排好序的第一部分中。
    插入排序的基本思想是：每步将一个待排序的记录，按其关键码值的大小插入前面已经排序的文件中适当位置上，直到全部插入完为止。

    Insertion sort is a simple sorting algorithm that builds the final sorted array (or list) one item at a time.
1.Set a marker for the sorted section after the first element
2.Repeat the following until unsorted section is empty:
(1)Select the first unsorted element
(2)Swap other elements to the right to create the correct position and shift the unsorted element.
(3)Advance the marker to the right one element

    算法复杂度：如果目标是把n个元素的序列升序排列，那么采用插入排序存在最好情况和最坏情况。最好情况就是，序列已经是升序排列了，在这种情况下，需要进行的比较操作需（n-1）次即可。最坏情况就是，序列是降序排列，那么此时需要进行的比较共有n(n-1)/2次。插入排序的赋值操作是比较操作的次数加上 (n-1）次。平均来说插入排序算法的时间复杂度为O(n^2）。因而，插入排序不适合对于数据量比较大的排序应用。但是，如果需要排序的数据量很小，例如，量级小于千，那么插入排序还是一个不错的选择。

    Algorithm Complexity: If the goal is to rank the sequences of n elements in ascending order, then there are best and worst cases for insert ordering. In the best case, the sequence is already in ascending order. In this case, the comparison operation that needs to be performed needs to be (n-1) times. The worst case is that the sequence is in descending order, then the comparisons that need to be made at this time are n(n-1)/2 times. The assignment operation for insert sorting is the number of comparison operations plus (n-1) times. On average, the time complexity of inserting the sorting algorithm is O(n^2). Thus, the insertion ordering is not suitable for sorting applications where the amount of data is relatively large. However, if the amount of data that needs to be sorted is small, for example, the magnitude is less than a thousand, then insert sorting is still a good choice.
/*END_OF_INSERTION_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_SHELL_SORT*/
    希尔排序(Shell's Sort)是插入排序的一种又称“缩小增量排序”（Diminishing Increment Sort），是直接插入排序算法的一种更高效的改进版本。希尔排序是非稳定排序算法。该方法因D.L.Shell于1959年提出而得名。
  希尔排序是把记录按下标的一定增量分组，对每组使用直接插入排序算法排序；随着增量逐渐减少，每组包含的关键词越来越多，当增量减至1时，整个文件恰被分成一组，算法便终止。

    Shellsort, also known as Shell sort or Shell's method, is an in-place comparison sort. It can be seen as either a generalization of sorting by exchange (bubble sort) or sorting by insertion (insertion sort).The method starts by sorting pairs of elements far apart from each other, then progressively reducing the gap between elements to be compared. Starting with far apart elements, it can move some out-of-place elements into position faster than a simple nearest neighbor exchange. Donald Shell published the first version of this sort in 1959.The running time of Shellsort is heavily dependent on the gap sequence it uses. For many practical variants, determining their time complexity remains an open problem.

    算法复杂度：依赖于增量序列的选择
好的增量序列的共同特征：
① 最后一个增量必须为1；
② 应该尽量避免序列中的值(尤其是相邻的值)互为倍数的情况。
有人通过大量的实验，给出了较好的结果：当n较大时，比较和移动的次数约在nl.25到1.6n1.25之间。
2．Shell排序的时间性能优于直接插入排序
希尔排序的时间性能优于直接插入排序的原因：
①当文件初态基本有序时直接插入排序所需的比较和移动次数均较少。
②当n值较小时，n和n²的差别也较小，即直接插入排序的最好时间复杂度O(n)和最坏时间复杂度0( n²)差别不大。
③在希尔排序开始时增量较大，分组较多，每组的记录数目少，故各组内直接插入较快，后来增量di逐渐缩小，分组数逐渐减少，而各组的记录数目逐渐增多，但由于已经按di-1作为距离排过序，使文件较接近于有序状态，所以新的一趟排序过程也较快。

    Algorithm complexity: dependent on the choice of incremental sequences
Common features of good incremental sequences:
1 The last increment must be 1;
2 You should try to avoid situations where the values ​​in the sequence (especially adjacent values) are multiples of each other.
Some people have given good results through a large number of experiments: when n is large, the number of comparisons and movements is between nl.25 and 1.6n1.25.
2. Shell sorting time performance is better than direct insert sorting
The time performance of Hill sorting is better than the reason for direct insert sorting:
1 When the initial state of the file is basically ordered, the comparison and movement times required for directly inserting the sort are small.
2 When the value of n is small, the difference between n and n2 is also small, that is, the best time complexity O(n) and the worst time complexity 0 (n2) of direct insertion ordering are not much different.
3 At the beginning of the sorting of the hill, the increment is larger, the grouping is more, and the number of records in each group is small, so the direct insertion in each group is faster, and then the increment di is gradually reduced, the number of groups is gradually reduced, and the number of records in each group is reduced. Gradually increasing, but because the di-1 has been sorted by distance, the file is closer to the ordered state, so the new one-order sorting process is also faster.
/*END_OF_SHELL_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_QUICK_SORT*/
    快速排序（Quicksort）是对冒泡排序的一种改进。
    快速排序由C. A. R. Hoare在1962年提出。它的基本思想是：通过一趟排序将要排序的数据分割成独立的两部分，其中一部分的所有数据都比另外一部分的所有数据都要小，然后再按此方法对这两部分数据分别进行快速排序，整个排序过程可以递归进行，以此达到整个数据变成有序序列。

    Quicksort (sometimes called partition-exchange sort) is an efficient sorting algorithm, serving as a systematic method for placing the elements of an array in order. Developed by Tony Hoare in 1959 and published in 1961,it is still a commonly used algorithm for sorting. When implemented well, it can be about two or three times faster than its main competitors, merge sort and heapsort.[contradictory]
    Quicksort is a comparison sort, meaning that it can sort items of any type for which a "less-than" relation (formally, a total order) is defined. In efficient implementations it is not a stable sort, meaning that the relative order of equal sort items is not preserved. Quicksort can operate in-place on an array, requiring small additional amounts of memory to perform the sorting. It is very similar to selection sort, except that it does not always choose worst-case partition.
    Mathematical analysis of quicksort shows that, on average, the algorithm takes O(n log n) comparisons to sort n items. In the worst case, it makes O(n2) comparisons, though this behavior is rare.

    算法复杂度：快速排序涉及到递归调用，所以该算法的时间复杂度还需要从递归算法的复杂度开始说起；最差的情况就是每一次取到的元素就是数组中最小/最大的，最优的情况就是每一次取到的元素都刚好平分整个数组。递归算法的时间复杂度公式：T[n] = aT[n/b] + f(n) 
首先就地快速排序使用的空间是O(1)的，也就是个常数级；而真正消耗空间的就是递归调用了，因为每次递归就要保持一些数据；最优的情况下空间复杂度为：O(logn)；每一次都平分数组的情况，最差的情况下空间复杂度为：O( n )，退化为冒泡排序的情况。

    Algorithm complexity: Quick sorting involves recursive calls, so the time complexity of the algorithm needs to start from the complexity of the recursive algorithm; the worst case is that each time the element is taken is the smallest/largest in the array, the most The good thing is that each time the elements are taken, they just split the entire array. Time complexity formula for recursive algorithm: T[n] = aT[n/b] + f(n)
First, the space used for in-place quick sorting is O(1), which is a constant level; the real space consumption is recursively called, because each recursion needs to maintain some data; in the optimal case, the space complexity is :O(logn); Each time the score group is flat, in the worst case, the space complexity is: O( n ), which degenerates into a bubble sort.
/*END_OF_QUICK_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_BUBBLE_SORT*/
    冒泡排序（Bubble Sort），是一种计算机科学领域的较简单的排序算法。
    它重复地走访过要排序的数列，一次比较两个元素，如果他们的顺序错误就把他们交换过来。走访数列的工作是重复地进行直到没有再需要交换，也就是说该数列已经排序完成。
    这个算法的名字由来是因为越大的元素会经由交换慢慢“浮”到数列的顶端，故名“冒泡排序”。

    Bubble sort, sometimes referred to as sinking sort, is a simple sorting algorithm that repeatedly steps through the list to be sorted, compares each pair of adjacent items and swaps them if they are in the wrong order. The pass through the list is repeated until no swaps are needed, which indicates that the list is sorted. The algorithm, which is a comparison sort, is named for the way smaller or larger elements "bubble" to the top of the list. Although the algorithm is simple, it is too slow and impractical for most problems even when compared to insertion sort.[2] Bubble sort can be practical if the input is in mostly sorted order with some out-of-order elements nearly in position.

    算法复杂度：若文件的初始状态是正序的，一趟扫描即可完成排序。所需的关键字比较次数C和记录移动次数 M均达到最小值:C=n-1，M=0。
所以，冒泡排序最好的时间复杂度为O（n）。
　　若初始文件是反序的，需要进行  趟排序。每趟排序要进行  次关键字的比较(1≤i≤n-1)，且每次比较都必须移动记录三次来达到交换记录位置。因此冒泡排序总的平均时间复杂度为O（n²）。

    Algorithm complexity: If the initial state of the file is positive, the scan can be done in one scan. The required number of keyword comparison times C and the number of recording movements M reach a minimum value: C=n-1, M=0.
Therefore, the best time complexity for bubble sorting is O(n).
If the initial file is reversed, you need to sort it. For each sorting, a comparison of the sub-keys is performed (1 ≤ i ≤ n-1), and each comparison must be moved three times to reach the exchange recording position. Therefore, the total average time complexity of bubble sorting is O(n2).
/*END_OF_BUBBLE_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_SHAKER_SORT*/
    鸡尾酒排序（Shaker Sort/Cocktail Sort），是一种改进的冒泡排序方法，亦称双向冒泡排序。
双向冒泡排序算法的运作如下：
传统冒泡气泡排序的双向进行，先让气泡排序由左向右进行，再来让气泡排序由右往左进行，如此完成一次排序的动作
使用left与right两个旗标来记录左右两端已排序的元素位置。

    Cocktail shaker sort, also known as bidirectional bubble sort, cocktail sort, shaker sort (which can also refer to a variant of selection sort), ripple sort, shuffle sort, or shuttle sort, is a variation of bubble sort that is both a stable sorting algorithm and a comparison sort. The algorithm differs from a bubble sort in that it sorts in both directions on each pass through the list. This sorting algorithm is only marginally more difficult to implement than a bubble sort, and solves the problem of turtles in bubble sorts. It provides only marginal performance improvements, and does not improve asymptotic performance; like the bubble sort, it is not of practical interest (insertion sort is preferred for simple sorts), though it finds some use in education.

    算法复杂度：不同的是排序的交换次数。某些情况下鸡尾酒排序比普通冒泡排序的交换次数少。比如{2,3,4,1},鸡尾酒排序只需交换2次，而冒泡排序需要三次。总体上，鸡尾酒排序可以获得比冒泡排序稍好的性能。但是完全逆序时，鸡尾酒排序与冒泡排序的效率都非常差。鸡尾酒排序最糟或是平均所花费的次数都是O(n²)，但如果序列在一开始已经大部分排序过的话，会接近O(n)。

    Algorithm complexity: The difference is the number of sorted exchanges. In some cases cocktail sorting is less frequent than regular bubble sorting. For example, {2,3,4,1}, the cocktail sorting only needs to be exchanged 2 times, and the bubble sorting takes three times. In general, cocktail sorting can achieve slightly better performance than bubbling sorting. However, when sorting completely, the efficiency of cocktail sorting and bubble sorting is very poor. The worst sorting of cocktails or the average number of times spent is O(n2), but if the sequence has been mostly sorted at the beginning, it will be close to O(n).
/*END_OF_SHAKER_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_SELECT_SORT*/
    选择排序（Selection sort）是一种简单直观的排序算法。它的工作原理是每一次从待排序的数据元素中选出最小（或最大）的一个元素，存放在序列的起始位置，直到全部待排序的数据元素排完。 选择排序是不稳定的排序方法（比如序列[5， 5， 3]第一次就将第一个[5]与[3]交换，导致第一个5挪动到第二个5后面）。

    Selection sort is a sorting algorithm, specifically an in-place comparison sort. It has O(n2) time complexity, making it inefficient on large lists, and generally performs worse than the similar insertion sort. Selection sort is noted for its simplicity, and it has performance advantages over more complicated algorithms in certain situations, particularly where auxiliary memory is limited.
    The algorithm divides the input list into two parts: the sublist of items already sorted, which is built up from left to right at the front (left) of the list, and the sublist of items remaining to be sorted that occupy the rest of the list. Initially, the sorted sublist is empty and the unsorted sublist is the entire input list. The algorithm proceeds by finding the smallest (or largest, depending on sorting order) element in the unsorted sublist, exchanging (swapping) it with the leftmost unsorted element (putting it in sorted order), and moving the sublist boundaries one element to the right.

    算法复杂度：选择排序的交换操作介于 0 和 (n - 1） 次之间。选择排序的比较操作为 n (n - 1） / 2 次之间。选择排序的赋值操作介于 0 和 3 (n - 1） 次之间。
比较次数O(n^2），比较次数与关键字的初始状态无关，总的比较次数N=(n-1）+(n-2）+...+1=n*(n-1）/2。交换次数O(n），最好情况是，已经有序，交换0次；最坏情况交换n-1次，逆序交换n/2次。交换次数比冒泡排序少多了，由于交换所需CPU时间比比较所需的CPU时间多，n值较小时，选择排序比冒泡排序快。

    Algorithm Complexity: The swap operation for selecting a sort is between 0 and (n - 1) times. Select the sorting comparison operation to be between n (n - 1) / 2 times. The assignment operation for selecting a sort is between 0 and 3 (n - 1) times.
The number of comparisons O(n^2), the number of comparisons is independent of the initial state of the keyword, and the total number of comparisons N=(n-1)+(n-2)+...+1=n*(n-1) /2. The number of exchanges O(n), preferably, is already ordered, exchanged 0 times; the worst case is exchanged n-1 times, and the reverse order is exchanged n/2 times. The number of exchanges is much less than the bubble sort. Since the CPU time required for the exchange is more than the CPU time required for comparison, when the value of n is small, the selection sort is faster than the bubble sort.
/*END_OF_SELECT_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_BINARY_INSERT_SORT*/
    二分法插入排序（binary insert sort）是在插入第i个元素时，对前面的0～i-1元素进行折半，先跟他们中间的那个元素比，如果小，则对前半再进行折半，否则对后半进行折半，直到left<right，然后再把第i个元素前1位与目标位置之间的所有元素后移，再把第i个元素放在目标位置上。

    Binary insertion sort employs a binary search to determine the correct location to insert new elements, and therefore performs [log2(n)]（[] means taking the max value） comparisons in the worst case, which is O(n log n). The algorithm as a whole still has a running time of O(n2) on average because of the series of swaps required for each insertion.
    The number of swaps can be reduced by calculating the position of multiple elements before moving them. For example, if the target position of two elements is calculated before they are moved into the right position, the number of swaps can be reduced by about 25% for random data. In the extreme case, this variant works similar to merge sort.
    A variant named binary merge sort uses a binary insertion sort to sort groups of 32 elements, followed by a final sort using merge sort. It combines the speed of insertion sort on small data sets with the speed of merge sort on large data sets.

    算法复杂度：二分查找的算法并不会因为等于某一个值而停止查找，它将查找整个序列直到start<=end条件不满足而得到插入的位置，所以对于长度为n的数组来说，比较次数为log2n ,时间复杂度为O（log2n）。二分插入排序的主要操作为比较+后移赋值，则：
最坏情况：每次都在有序序列的起始位置插入，则整个有序序列的元素需要后移，时间复杂度为O（n^2）
最好情况：待排序数组本身就是正序的，每个元素所在位置即为它的插入位置，此时时间复杂度仅为比较时的时间复杂度，为O(log2n)
平均情况：O（n^2）
空间复杂度上， 二分插入排序也是就地排序算法，它的空间复杂度为O（1）.

    Algorithm complexity: The binary search algorithm does not stop the search because it is equal to a certain value. It will find the entire sequence until the start<=end condition is not satisfied and get the inserted position, so for the array of length n, compare The number of times is log2n and the time complexity is O(log2n). The main operation of binary insertion sorting is to compare + post shift assignment, then:
Worst case: Each time you insert at the beginning of an ordered sequence, the elements of the entire ordered sequence need to be shifted back, with a time complexity of O(n^2)
The best case: the array to be sorted is positively ordered, and the position of each element is its insertion position. At this time, the time complexity is only the time complexity of comparison, which is O(log2n).
Average case: O(n^2)
In terms of spatial complexity, binary insertion ordering is also an in-situ sorting algorithm, and its spatial complexity is O(1).
/*END_OF_BINARY_INSERT_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_HEAP_SORT*/
    堆排序(Heapsort)是指利用堆积树（堆）这种数据结构所设计的一种排序算法，它是选择排序的一种。可以利用数组的特点快速定位指定索引的元素。堆分为大根堆和小根堆，是完全二叉树。大根堆的要求是每个节点的值都不大于其父节点的值，即A[PARENT[i]] >= A[i]。在数组的非降序排序中，需要使用的就是大根堆，因为根据大根堆的要求可知，最大的值一定在堆顶。

    Heapsort is a comparison-based sorting algorithm. Heapsort can be thought of as an improved selection sort: like that algorithm, it divides its input into a sorted and an unsorted region, and it iteratively shrinks the unsorted region by extracting the largest element and moving that to the sorted region. The improvement consists of the use of a heap data structure rather than a linear-time search to find the maximum.
    Although somewhat slower in practice on most machines than a well-implemented quicksort, it has the advantage of a more favorable worst-case O(n log n) runtime. Heapsort is an in-place algorithm, but it is not a stable sort.
    Heapsort was invented by J. W. J. Williams in 1964. This was also the birth of the heap, presented already by Williams as a useful data structure in its own right.In the same year, R. W. Floyd published an improved version that could sort an array in-place, continuing his earlier research into the treesort algorithm.

    算法复杂度：初始化建堆过程时间：O（n）。首先要理解怎么计算这个堆化过程所消耗的时间，可以直接画图去理解；假设高度为k，则从倒数第二层右边的节点开始，这一层的节点都要执行子节点比较然后交换（如果顺序是对的就不用交换）；倒数第三层呢，则会选择其子节点进行比较和交换，如果没交换就可以不用再执行下去了。如果交换了，那么又要选择一支子树进行比较和交换；那么总的时间计算为：s = 2^( i - 1 )  *  ( k - i )；其中 i 表示第几层，2^( i - 1) 表示该层上有多少个元素，( k - i) 表示子树上要比较的次数，如果在最差的条件下，就是比较次数后还要交换；因为这个是常数，所以提出来后可以忽略。
综合可得S = n - longn -1，所以时间复杂度为：O(n)

    Algorithm complexity: Initializing the build process time: O(n). First of all, we must understand how to calculate the time consumed by this heaping process, which can be directly drawn to understand; assuming a height of k, starting from the node on the right side of the penultimate layer, the nodes of this layer must perform sub-node comparison and then exchange ( If the order is correct, there is no need to exchange); in the third to last, the child nodes are selected for comparison and exchange. If there is no exchange, they can be executed without further execution. If it is exchanged, then choose a subtree for comparison and exchange; then the total time is calculated as: s = 2^( i - 1 ) * ( k - i ); where i is the first layer, 2^( i - 1) indicates how many elements are on the layer, and ( k - i) indicates the number of times to be compared on the subtree. If it is under the worst condition, it is exchanged after the number of comparisons; because this is a constant, so Can be ignored after coming out.
Syntheticly available S = n - longn -1, so the time complexity is: O(n)
/*END_OF_HEAP_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_MERGE_SORT*/
    归并排序（MERGE-SORT）是建立在归并操作上的一种有效的排序算法,该算法是采用分治法的一个非常典型的应用。将已有序的子序列合并，得到完全有序的序列；即先使每个子序列有序，再使子序列段间有序。若将两个有序表合并成一个有序表，称为二路归并。

    Merge sort (also commonly spelled mergesort) is an efficient, general-purpose, comparison-based sorting algorithm. Most implementations produce a stable sort, which means that the implementation preserves the input order of equal elements in the sorted output. Merge sort is a divide and conquer algorithm that was invented by John von Neumann in 1945. A detailed description and analysis of bottom-up mergesort appeared in a report by Goldstine and von Neumann as early as 1948.

    算法复杂度：时间复杂度为O(nlog₂n) 这是该算法中最好、最坏和平均的时间性能。空间复杂度为 O(n)，比较操作的次数介于(nlogn) / 2和nlogn - n + 1。赋值操作的次数是(2nlogn)。归并算法的空间复杂度为：0 (n)。归并排序比较占用内存，但却是一种效率高且稳定的算法。

    Algorithm complexity: time complexity is O(nlog2n) This is the best, worst, and average time performance of the algorithm. The space complexity is O(n), and the number of comparison operations is between (nlogn) / 2 and nlogn - n + 1. The number of assignment operations is (2nlogn). The spatial complexity of the merge algorithm is: 0 (n). Merge sorting takes up memory, but it is an efficient and stable algorithm.
/*END_OF_MERGE_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_RADIX_SORT*/
    基数排序（Radix sort）属于“分配式排序”，又称“桶子法”或bin sort，顾名思义，它是透过键值的部份资讯，将要排序的元素分配至某些“桶”中，藉以达到排序的作用，基数排序法是属于稳定性的排序，其时间复杂度为O (nlog(r)m)，其中r为所采取的基数，而m为堆数，在某些时候，基数排序法的效率高于其它的稳定性排序法。

    Radix sort is a non-comparative integer sorting algorithm that sorts data with integer keys by grouping keys by the individual digits which share the same significant position and value. A positional notation is required, but because integers can represent strings of characters (e.g., names or dates) and specially formatted floating point numbers, radix sort is not limited to integers. Radix sort dates back as far as 1887 to the work of Herman Hollerith on tabulating machines.

    算法复杂度：该算法所花的时间基本是在把元素分配到桶里和把元素从桶里串起来；把元素分配到桶里：循环 length 次；把元素从桶里串起来：这个计算有点麻烦，看似两个循环，其实第二循环是根据桶里面的元素而定的，可以表示为：k×buckerCount；其中 k 表示某个桶中的元素个数，buckerCount  则表示存放元素的桶个数；
    有几种特殊情况：
    第一、所有的元素都存放在一个桶内：k = length，buckerCount = 1；
    第二、所有的元素平均分配到每个桶中：k = length/ bukerCount，buckerCount = 10；（这里已经固定了10个桶）
    所以平均情况下收集部分所花的时间为：length （也就是元素长度 n）
    综上所述：
    时间复杂度为：posCount * (length  + length) ；其中 posCount 为数组中最大元素的最高位数；简化下得：O( k*n ) ；其中k为常数，n为元素个数；
    空间复杂度：该算法的空间复杂度就是在分配元素时，使用的桶空间；所以空间复杂度为：O（10 × length）= O （length）

    Algorithm complexity: The time spent by the algorithm is basically to allocate elements to the bucket and string the elements from the bucket; assign the elements to the bucket: cycle length times; string the elements from the bucket: this calculation is a bit Trouble, it seems like two loops, in fact, the second loop is based on the elements in the bucket, can be expressed as: k × buckerCount; where k is the number of elements in a bucket, buckerCount is the bucket of the storage element number;
    There are several special cases:
    First, all elements are stored in a bucket: k = length, buckerCount = 1;
    Second, all elements are evenly distributed into each bucket: k = length / bukerCount, buckerCount = 10; (10 buckets have been fixed here)
    So the average time spent collecting parts is: length (that is, element length n)
    In summary:
    The time complexity is: posCount * (length + length) ; where posCount is the highest number of bits of the largest element in the array; simplified: O( k * n ) ; where k is a constant and n is the number of elements;
    Spatial complexity: The spatial complexity of the algorithm is the bucket space used when assigning elements; so the space complexity is: O(10 × length) = O 
/*END_OF_RADIX_SORT*/
/*BEGIN_OF_COUNT_SORT*/
    计数排序（Counting sort）是一个非基于比较的排序算法，该算法于1954年由 Harold H. Seward 提出。它的优势在于在对一定范围内的整数排序时，它的复杂度为Ο(n+k)（其中k是整数的范围），快于任何比较排序算法。 [1-2]  当然这是一种牺牲空间换取时间的做法，而且当O(k)>O(n*log(n))的时候其效率反而不如基于比较的排序（基于比较的排序的时间复杂度在理论上的下限是O(n*log(n)), 如归并排序，堆排序）

    Counting sort is an algorithm for sorting a collection of objects according to keys that are small integers; that is, it is an integer sorting algorithm. It operates by counting the number of objects that have each distinct key value, and using arithmetic on those counts to determine the positions of each key value in the output sequence. Its running time is linear in the number of items and the difference between the maximum and minimum key values, so it is only suitable for direct use in situations where the variation in keys is not significantly greater than the number of items. However, it is often used as a subroutine in another sorting algorithm, radix sort, that can handle larger keys more efficiently.

    算法复杂度：计数排序对输入的数据有附加的限制条件：
1、输入的线性表的元素属于有限偏序集S；
2、设输入的线性表的长度为n，|S|=k（表示集合S中元素的总数目为k），则k=O(n)。
在这两个条件下，计数排序的复杂性为O(n)。
时间复杂度
    时间复杂度可以很好的看出了就是：O( n )；
空间复杂度
    空间复杂度也可以很好的看出来：O( n )；
    计数排序的时间复杂度和空间复杂度都是非常有效的，但是该算法对输入的元素有限制要求，所以并不是所有的排序都使用该算法；最好的是0～9之间的数值差不会很大的数据元素间比较；有人会说这个没多大用，但是在后面的基数排序中会看到，这可以算是基数排序中的一个基础。

    Algorithm complexity: Count sorting has additional restrictions on the input data:
1. The elements of the input linear table belong to a finite partial order set S;
2. Let the length of the input linear table be n, |S|=k (indicating that the total number of elements in the set S is k), then k=O(n).
Under these two conditions, the complexity of counting sorting is O(n).
time complexity
     The time complexity can be seen very well: O( n );
Space complexity
     The spatial complexity can also be seen very well: O( n );
     The time complexity and space complexity of counting sorting are very effective, but the algorithm has restrictions on the input elements, so not all sorting uses the algorithm; the best is the numerical difference between 0 and 9. There won't be a lot of comparison between data elements; some would say that this is not very useful, but will be seen in the cardinal sorting that follows, which can be considered as a basis for cardinality sorting.
/*END_OF_COUNT_SORT*/